{
    "id": "ee3069e3f9594fd0a62eec5f5dd36e0c",
    "title": "Make, Force, Allow, Let",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They ...................................... me wait outside.",
            "description": "Made is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "forced",
                "allowed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e6d7d0104c44b00a5637f434f3d87ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ..................................... me to sign the papers.",
            "description": "Forced is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "forced",
                "made",
                "allowed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "082a943fe5544f6da15e009ef1ac3927"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was not ...................................... to visit him.",
            "description": "Allowed is followed by a to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "allowed",
                "let"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "236892ac17e24c27917791f21dc2b70a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .......................................... me to accept the offer.",
            "description": "Force is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "forced",
                "let"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "92cdf914584e4a72a6e6d8f5e5766beb"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are not ....................................... to smoke in public places.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "allowed",
                "made",
                "let"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d6ac568f99644d23ae3db7a2a8bac784"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will they .................................... us to wait here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "allow",
                "let",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b1b2c332c054719815d1019140dc488"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ...................................... them come in.",
            "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "allow",
                "let",
                "force"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f927cd0ecf0347b7929665cdb180fbcd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ....................................... to apologize for his mistakes.",
            "description": "Either made or forced is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "forced",
                "allowed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "63d3ed703047426b9f4cf8b96455abf7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ............................................... to retract her statements.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "allowed",
                "forced"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9f89925d511d4e1887c63532c7da8e95"
        },
        {
            "question": "We do not .......................................... people to smoke in the kitchen",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "let",
                "allow",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e293d63a51a440369a1e8a04e1c24987"
        },
        {
            "question": "I found it difficult to ........................................ myself understood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "force",
                "make",
                "allow"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "524de1f16f7f49f79f219924ff2ee8dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………….. to leave work early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "allowed",
                "let"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "febe4b481ed844239212210c910d028c"
        }
    ]
}